Sometimes, we would like to fit models where
有时我们会拟合模型
the response is not linearly related to the explanatory variable.
即使反应变量与解释变量并没有线性相关性
We can do this with what are known as higher order terms.
我们可以使用所谓的高阶项完成
Higher order terms include quadratics,
高阶项包括二项式
cubics, interactions, and many other relationships.
三项式 交叉项和其他许多关系
In order to add these terms to our linear models,
为了把这些项添加到线性模型中
we can simply multiply our columns by one another.
我们只需要把列乘以另一列
Here, we can create a quadratic relationship for the number of bedrooms,
这里我们创建了卧室数量的二次关系
by either squaring all the values in
通过卧室所有值的平方
the bedrooms column or by multiplying the column by itself.
或列乘以列
Let's store this in bedrooms squared.
我们存储为卧室的平方
When we add these higher order terms into our models,
我们把这些高阶项添加到模型中
we also need to include the lower order terms.
也需要加入低阶项
Let's try predicting the price using bedrooms and bedrooms squared.
我们来使用卧室和卧室的平方来预测价格
We're going to create our intercept again.
再次创建截距
We need to predict our response which is the price.
我们需要预测反应变量 即价格
We're going to do this using bedrooms, using intercepts.
使用卧室作为截距来完成
Here, we can take a look at the results.
这里我们可以观察到结果
Notice, that adding the quadratic means that we can not interpret
注意 添加二项式表明我们不会
this coefficient attached to the bedrooms the same way that we could earlier.
采取之前相同的方式解释卧室相关的系数
That is, this coefficient isn't
即系数并不是
the predicted change in price for each additional bedroom any longer,
随着卧室增多 所预测的价格也发生变化
because changing the bedroom and this term also means changing it in the quadratic term.
因为改变卧室数量和这一项 也表明二项式中发生变化
So the change in price is dependent on the starting and ending number of bedrooms.
所以价格改变取决于卧室的初始和最终数量
The change in price for changing from
卧室数量从 3 个变为 4 个时价格的变化
three to four bedrooms isn't the same as changing from five to six bedrooms.
与从 5 个变为 6 个时价格的变化不一样
So neither of these terms is easily interpreted.
所以无法简单解释这些项
We could also add a cubic term to our dataset, like this.
我们也可以向数据集中添加这样的三项式
Here, I'm going to call this bedrooms cubed.
这里我命名为卧室的立方
And then, we might add it to our model like this.
然后像这样添加到模型中
Just steal this part,
截取这一部分
and then we have this cubed portion.
然后我们得到立方后的结果
So I'm just going to add that, here.
我添加到这里
So then we can look at our results.
然后我们来观察下结果
Here, you can see that the R-squared actually increased by a little bit.
这里你会发现 R 平方实际上只增加了一点
However, that's not a very substantial amount for including this cube number of bedrooms.
不过加入卧室的立方值并不是很大的数字
It's probably not appropriate to think that
认为卧室的立方值与价格具有相关性
the cubed value of the bedrooms is actually associated with the price,
并不恰当
but we'll discuss this more later.
不过接下来我们还会继续探究这个问题
Additionally, each of these coefficients down here isn't interpreted in a nice way.
另外下面每个系数都不能很好地得到解释
Let's now look at an interaction term.
现在我们来看一下交叉项
An interaction term is created by multiplying
交叉项是通过两个变量相乘
two variables by one another to add to your linear model.
得到的 可以添加到线性模型中
Let's create an interaction between the area and the number of bedrooms.
我们来创建面积和卧室数量之间的交互项
We'll add this into our data frame for this dataset.
然后把它添加到这个数据集的DataFrame中
Now, to add the interaction terms to our model,
现在为了把交叉项添加到模型中
we should again add the lower order terms.
我们应该再次添加低阶项
This means adding both the area and the bedrooms into our linear model.
这意味着把面积和卧室数量都添加到线性模型中
Since the number of bedrooms is already in our model,
既然卧室数量已经包含在模型中
I'm just going to add the area as well as the interaction term.
我这里添加面积和交叉项
Great. So here, you can see there's a substantial improvement.
非常棒 这里你看到发生了巨大提升
In the next video, you'll get a closer look
在接下来的视频中你将仔细观察
at how we know we should add one of these terms.
我们如何知道应该添加其中一项